Mercury Press Records
Mercury Press Records
- Manuscripts (Part I)
  - Carr, Terry
    - Brown Robert, July 1962; article (Box 14)
    - Hop-Friend, Nov. 1962; article (Box 14)
    - Touchstone, Aug. 1964; article (Box 14)
  - Carroll, Lewis
    - Photography Extraordinary, Oct. 1957; article (Box 14)
  - Carter, Lin
    - Uncollected Works, Feb. 1965; article (Box 14)
  - Chandler, Bertram
    - The Cage, June 1957; article (Box 14)
    - Critical Angle, Nov. 1958; article (Box 14)
    - The Man Who Could Not Stop, May 1959; article (Box 14)
  - Chapman, Vic
    - Come Back Elena, Oct. 1966; article (Box 14)
  - Charteris, Leslie
    - The Convenient Monster, March 1965 (Box 14)
    - The Questing Tycoon, June 1958; article (Box 14)
  - Cheinisse, Claude F.
    - Juliette, July 1961; article (Box 14)
  - Chekhov, Anton
    - The Flying Islands, April 1959; article (Box 14)
  - Christopher, John
    - A Few Kindred Spirits, Sept. 1965; article (Box 14)
  - Clarke, Arthur
    - Cosmic Casanova, March 1958; article (Box 14)
    - A Crime on Mars, June 1961; article (Box 14)
    - Inside the Comet, Oct. 1960; article (Box 14)
    - Of Mind and Matter, Oct. 1958; article (Box 14)
    - Security Check, Sept. 1957; article (Box 14)
    - Saturn Rising, 1961; article (Box 14)
    - Venture to the Moon (Parts I, II, III), Dec. 1956-Feb. 1957 (Box 14)
  - Cleeve, Brian, article
    - The Devil and Democracy, Nov. 1966; article (Box 14)
  - Clifton, Mark
    - Remembrance and Reflections, June 1958; book (Box 14)
    - What Now, Little Man, Oct. 1959; book (Box 14)
  - Clingerman, Mildred
    - The Day of the Green Velvet Cloak, July 1958; article (Box 14)
    - First Lesson, Dec. 1956; article (Box 14)
    - The Little Witch of Elm Street, April 1957; article (Box 14)
    - Measure My Love, Dec. 1962; article (Box 14)
    - A Red Heart and Blue Roses, April 1964; article (Box 14)
    - The Wild Wood, Jan. 1957; article (Box 14)
  - Clinton, Ed. M.
    - Heir Apparent, Sept. 1966; article (Box 15)
    - The Third Dragon, May 1966; article (Box 15)
  - Cockburn, Claud
    - Send-Off, June 1959; article (Box 15)
  - Cogswell, Theodore R.
    - Aces Loaded, July 1957; article (Box 15)
    - The Burning, July 1960; article (Box 15)
    - The Cabbage Patch, Dec. 1957; article (Box 15)
    - Things, May 1958; article (Box 15)
    - You Know Willie, May 1957; article (Box 15)
    - The Roper, Aug. 1962; article (Box 15)
  - Cole, Les
    - A Man of the World, Jan. 1957; article (Box 15)
  - Collier, John
    - After the Ball, Nov. 1959; article (Box 15)
    - Man Overboard, March 1960; article (Box 15)
    - The Tender Age, May 1960; article (Box 15)
    - A Word to the Wise, Sept. 1958; article (Box 15)
  - Connable, Alfred
    - The Secret Flight of Friendship Eleven, Nov. 1962; article (Box 15)
  - Contoski, Victor
    - Von Goom's Gambit, Dec. 1966; article (Box 15)
  - Corwin, M.
    - Query for Doc Richards, Nov. 1958; poem (Box 15)
  - Correa, Hugo
    - The Last Element, April 1962; article (Box 15)
  - Coupling, J.J.
    - In 2063 She Ceased to Be, July 1959; article (Box 15)
  - Crawford, Deborah
    - Short Cut, April 1965; poem (Box 15)
  - Crossen, Kendell F.
    - The Golden Flask, Jan. 1962; poem (Box 15)
  - Crow, Levi
    - The Hairy Thunderer, Feb. 1960; article (Box 15)
  - Cunnington, Mrs. Allen and John
    - Up, Down, and Sideways, Sept. 1959; article (Box 15)
  - Damonti, Henri
    - The Notary and the Conspiracy, Dec. 1962; article (Box 15)
  - Daniell, Sally
    - An Extraordinary Child, Oct. 1966; article (Box 15)
  - Davidson, Avram
    - Apres Nous, March 1960; article (Box 15)
    - Author, Author, July 1959; article (Box 15)
    - Bumberboom, Dec. 1966; article (Box 15)
    - Dagon, Oct. 1959; article (Box 15)
    - Fade Out, 1963; article (Box 15)
    - The Grantha Sighting, April 1958; article (Box 15)
    - Great is Diana, June 1958; article (Box 15)
    - The House The Blakeneys Built, Jan. 1964; article (Box 15)
    - I Do Not Hear You, Sir, Feb. 1958; article (Box 15)
    - Jury-Rig, Nov. 1957; article (Box 15)
    - The Kappa Nu Nexus, Aug. 1961; article (Box 15)
    - The Montevarde Camera, April 1959; article (Box 15)
    - Mirror, Mirror, Oct. 1965; article (Box 15)
    - Miss Buttermouth, March 1962; article (Box 15)
    - Now Let Us Sleep, Sept. 1957; article (Box 15)
    - Or The Grasses Grow, Nov. 1958; article (Box 15)
    - Sacheverell, March 1964; article (Box 15)
    - The Sixth Season, June 1960; article (Box 15)
    - The Sources of the Nile, Jan. 1961; article (Box 15)
    - Summerland, July 1957; article (Box 15)
    - The Teeth of Despair, May 1961; article (Box 15)
    - The Unknown Law, June 1964; article (Box 15)
    - Up the Close and Down the Stair, May 1958; article (Box 16)
    - The Vat, Oct. 1961; article (Box 16)
    - What Strange Stars and Skies, 1963; article (Box 16)
    - Where Do You Live, Queen Esther?, Nov. 1964; article (Box 16)
    - Yo-Ho, and Up, Aug. 1960; article (Box 16)
    - Rogue Dragon, July 1965; article (Box 16)
    - Book reviews, 1963-1964 (Box 16)
  - Davis, Hassoldt
    - The Pleasant Woman, Eve, Sept. 1959; article (Box 16)
  - de Camp, L. Sprague
    - Dragon Hunt, 1963; article (Box 16)
    - How to Plan a Fauna, 1963; article (Box 16)
    - How to Talk Futurian, Oct. 1957; article (Box 16)
    - The Gods, poem (Box 16)
  - de Cles, Jon
    - Cantabile, article (Box 16)
    - Forgive Us Our Debtors, article (Box 16)
    - The Picture Window, article (Box 16)
  - de Ford, Miriam Allen
    - The Absolutely Perfect Murder, Dec. 1965; article (Box 16)
    - Against Authority, Feb. 1966; article (Box 16)
    - All in Good Time, June 1960; article (Box 16)
    - The Apotheosis of Ki, Sept. 1956; article (Box 16)
    - The Cage, June 1961; article (Box 16)
    - The Colony, April 1966; article (Box 16)
    - The Expendables, July 1965; article (Box 16)
    - Feather Bed on Chlyntha, Nov. 1957; article (Box 16)
    - First Dig, April 1959; article (Box 16)
    - Gathi, June 1958; article (Box 16)
    - The Green Snow, Oct. 1966; article (Box 16)
    - The Monster, Aug. 1960; article (Box 16)
    - Rope's End, Sept. 1960; article (Box 16)
    - Slips Take Over, Aug. 1964; article (Box 16)
    - Timequake, June 1958; article (Box 16)
    - The Transit of Venus, June 1962; article (Box 16)
    - The Voyage of the Deborah Pratt, undated; article (Box 16)
  - del Rey, Lester
    - Lady of Space, July 1958; article (Box 17)
    - Little Jimmy, April 1957; article (Box 17)
    - Robots Should Be Seen, Jan. 1958; article (Box 17)
    - The Seat of Judgment, July 1957; article (Box 17)
  - Demmon, Calvin W.
    - Fred, 1963; article (Box 17)
    - Switch, Oct. 1965; article (Box 17)
  - Derleth, August
    - The Dark Boy, 1957, Feb., articles (Box 17)
  - De Vet, Charles
    - Return Journey, Dec. 1961; articles (Box 17)
  - Dick, Philip K.
    - We Can Remember it for You Wholesale, March 1966; article (Box 17)
  - Dickinson, Joseph
    - Three For the Stars, April 1962; article (Box 17)
  - Dickson, Gordon R.
    - The Amulet, Jan. 1959; article (Box 17)
    - Break Through Gang, Dec. 1965; article (Box 17)
    - Brother Charlie, July 1958; article (Box 17)
    - Button, Button, Sept. 1960; article (Box 17)
    - The Christmas Present, Jan. 1958; article (Box 17)
    - Fleegl of Fleegl, May 1958; article (Box 17)
    - Friend for Life, March 1957; article (Box 17)
    - The Haunted Village, Aug. 1961; article (Box 17)
    - The Last Dream, July 1960; article (Box 17)
    - A Matter of Technique, May 1958; article (Box 17)
    - One on Trial, April 1960; article (Box 17)
    - Rescue Mission, Jan. 1957; article (Box 17)
    - Roofs of Silver, Dec. 1962; article (Box 17)
    - Salmanazar, Aug. 1962; article (Box 17)
    - The Three Tentacled Mr. Usussis, Nov. 1956; article (Box 17)
    - With Butter and Mustard, Dec. 1957; article (Box 17)
    - The Game of Fire, April 1960; book (Box 17)
    - The Immortal, Aug. 1965; book (Box 17)
    - Naked to the Stars (Part I, Part II), Oct.-Nov. 1961; book (Box 18)
    - The Guided Tour, March 1959; poem (Box 18)
  - Disch, Thomas M.
    - Doubting Thomas, June 1966; article (Box 18)
    - Nada, Aug. 1964; article (Box 18)
    - Dorman, S.
    - The Deepest Blue in the World, July 1964; article (Box 18)
    - Winged Victory, 1963; article (Box 18)
  - Drake, Leah Bodine
    - Time and the Sphinx (In memory of Lord Dunsany), Jan. 1965; article (Box 18)
    - A Meeting on a Northern Moor, July 1961; poem (Box 18)
    - New Wine in an Old Bottle, July 1959; poem (Box 18)
    - We Move on Turning Stone, July 1957; poem (Box 18)
    - The Word of Willow, Dec. 1957; poem (Box 18)
  - Draper, Hal
    - The Day Civilization Collapsed, June 1961; article (Box 18)
  - Drury, Allen
    - Something, Oct. 1960; article (Box 18)
  - Eastlake, William
    - What Nice Hands Held, Dec. 1961; article (original publication in Kenyon Review) (Box 18)
  - Edmondson, G.C.
    - Rescue, June 1957; article (Box 18)
    - The Country Boy, Jan. 1961; article (Box 18)
    - From Caribou to Carry Nation, April 1959; article (Box 18)
    - The Galactic Calabash, Dec. 1960; article (Box 18)
    - The Inferlab Project, Dec. 1957; article (Box 18)
    - Renaissance, Dec. 1957; article (Box 18)
    - Ringer, April 1960; article (Box 18)
    - The Sign of the Goose, Aug. 1960 (Box 18)
    - The Status Quo Peddlers, Sept. 1957; article (Box 18)
    - The Third Bubble, undated; article (Box 18)
    - The World Must Never Know, 1963; article (Box 18)
  - Elliott, George P.
    - Among the Dang, 1950; article (printed in Esquire org.) (Box 18)
    - Fag, 1961; article (printed in Among the Songs org.) (Box 18)
    - The NRACP, Aug. 1960; article (printed copy) (Box 18)
    - Sandra, Oct. 1957; article (Box 18)
  - Ellis, H.F.
    - Fireside Talk, June 1960; article (Box 18)
  - Ellison, Harlan
    - Poulie Charmed the Sleeping Woman, Aug. 1962; article (Box 18)
  - Emshwiller, Carol
    - Adapted, May 1961; article (Box 19)
    - Baby, Feb. 1958; article (Box 19)
    - But Soft, What Light, April 1966; article (Box 19)
    - The Coming, May 1957; article (Box 19)
    - Pelts, Nov. 1958; article (Box 19)
    - Summer Weekend, Aug. 1959; article (Box 19)
    - You'll Feel Better, July 1957; article (Box 19)
  - Etchison, Dennis
    - A Nice, Shady Place, Aug. 1964; article (Box 19)
  - Faine, Djinn
    - Daughter of Eve, June 1962; article (Box 19)
  - Farmer, Philip Jose'
    - The Alley Man, June 1959; article (Box 19)
    - The Night of Light, June 1957; article (Box 19)
    - Open to Me, My Sister, May 1960; article (Box 19)
    - The Strange Birth, May 1962; article (Box 19)
    - Prometheus, March 1961; book (galley) (Box 19)
  - Fast, Howard
    - Cato the Martian, June 1960; article (Box 19)
    - The Cold, Cold Box, July 1959; article (Box 19)
    - The First Men, Feb. 1960; article (Box 19)
    - The Martian Shop, Oct. 1959; article (Box 19)
    - The Sight of Eden, Oct. 1960; article (Box 19)
  - Fast, Julius
    - Grow Old Along With Me, 1966; article (Box 19)
  - Fennel, Erik
    - Night Sky of Venus, May 1957; article (Box 19)
  - Fessier, Michael
    - Bewitched, Nov. 1958; article (Box 19)
    - The Blue Eyed Horse, July 1958; article (Box 19)
  - Findlay, D.K.
    - The Way Back, Feb. 1966; article (Box 19)
  - Finney, Charles G.
    - The Black Retriever, Oct. 1958; article (Box 19)
    - The Captivity, Oct. 1961; article (Box 19)
    - The Gilashrikes, Oct. 1959; article (Box 19)
    - The Horse-Napping of Hotspur, Aug. 1958; article (Box 19)
    - The Iowan's Curse, June 1958; article (Box 19)
  - Fish, Robert L.
    - Not Counting Bridges, 1963; article (Box 20)
    - Sonny, May 1965; article (Box 20)
  - Fitzpatrick, R.C.
    - On The House, Nov. 1964; article (Box 20)
  - Fontenay, Charles L.
    - Blind Alley, undated; article (Box 20)
    - A Summer After Noon, Dec. 1958; article (Box 20)
    - Up, March 1959; article (Box 20)
  - Forester, C.S.
    - Marjorie is Still Waiting, Aug. 1958; article (Box 20)
  - Foster, Charles
    - The Trouble Makers, undated; article (original publication in Evergreen Review) (Box 20)
  - Franke, Herbert W.
    - The Man Who Feared Robots, 1963; article (Box 20)
  - Frazee, Eric
    - Noselrubb, The Tree, May 1962; article (Box 20)
  - Friedberg, Gertrude
    - The Short Happy Death of George Franklin, 1963; article (Box 20)
  - Fritch, Charles E.
    - Big Wide Wonderful World, Feb. 1958; article (Box 20)
  - Friedman, Bruce
    - Yes We Have No Richard, Nov. 1960; article (Box 20)
  - Garrett, Randall
    - Masters of the Metropolis, April 1957; article (Box 20)
    - Spatial Relationship, Aug. 1962; article (Box 20)
    - Something Rich and Strange, June 1961; article (Box 20)
    - Witness for the Persecution, Jan. 1966; article (Box 20)
    - Backward, Turn Backwards, 1960, Nov., poet (Box 20)
    - Hot Argument, Nov. 1960; poem (Box 20)
    - Pop!, Nov. 1960; poem (Box 20)
    - Zap, 1963; poem (Box 20)
  - Gastildi, Ernesto
    - The End of Eternity, March 1965; article (Box 20)
  - Gilien, Sasha
    - Ad Finitum, Dec. 1962; article (Box 20)
    - El Numero Uno, undated; article (Box 20)
    - Two's A Crowd, July 1962; article (Box 20)
  - Glaser, Alice
    - The Tunnel, Sept. 1961; article (Box 20)
  - Godwin, Tom
    - The Harvest, July 1957; article (Box 20)
    - Survival, undated; book (Box 20)
  - Gold, Herbert
    - The Day They Got Boston, Sept. 1961; article (Box 20)
    - The Mirror and Mr. Sneeves, Dec. 1961; article (Box 20)
    - Man of Parts, April 1966; article (Box 20)
  - Gold, Horace
    - What Price Wings, Dec. 1962; article (Box 20)
  - Goldsmith, Ruth M.
    - Moonshine, June 1957; article (original publication in Atlantic, 1956) (Box 20)
  - Goulart, Ron
    - Breakaway House, May 1966; article (Box 21)
    - Chameleon, Sept. 1964; article (Box 21)
    - ...and Curiouser, March 1958; article (Box 21)
    - Dream Girl, Nov. 1958; article (Box 21)
    - Experiment in Autobiography, July 1966; article (Box 21)
    - The Katy Dialogues, July 1958; article (Box 21)
    - Kearny's Last Case, Sept. 1965; article (Box 21)
    - Namara's Fish, 1963; article (Box 21)
    - A New Lo!, Jan. 1958; article (Box 21)
    - Please Stand By, Jan. 1962; article (Box 21)
    - Princess 122, May 1962; article (Box 21)
    - Rake, June 1965; article (Box 21)
    - Ralph Wollstonecraft: A Memoir, Nov. 1959; article (Box 21)
    - To The Rescue, Jan. 1966; article (Box 21)
    - Uncle Arly, July 1962; article (Box 21)
    - Book reviews, undated (Box 21)
  - Grass, Mathew
    - The Snake in the Closet, Jan. 1962; article (Box 21)
  - Graves, Robert
    - Dead Man's Bottles, Feb. 1961; article (original publication in Occupation: Writer, 1950) (Box 21)
    - The Shout, May 1959; article (Box 21)
  - Green, Robert M., Jr.
    - The Deadeye Dick Syndrome, Feb. 1965; article (Box 21)
    - No Place Like Where, April 1964; article (Box 21)
    - Apology to Inky, Jan. 1966; book (Box 21)
  - Gunn, James E.
    - Skin Game, July 1958; article (Box 21)
    - Not So Great an Enemy, July 1957; book (Box 21)
    - Space is a Lonely Place, May 1957; book (Box 21)
  - Gunther, Max
    - Municipal Dump, Sept. 1966; article (Box 22)
  - Guttridge, Len
    - Aunt Millicent at the Races, April 1964; article (Box 22)
    - The Most Wonderful News, Jan. 1966; article (Box 22)
    - A Quest for Uplift, June 1966; article (Box 22)
  - Hamilton, Leigh Brackett
    - All the Colors of the Rainbow, June 1957; article (Box 22)
  - Hamilton, Edmond
    - The Dark Backward, May 1958; article (Box 22)
    - No Earth Man I, Nov. 1957; article (Box 22)
    - The Pro, Oct. 1964; article (Box 22)
  - Hansen, Joseph
    - Ballad of the Red Giants, Dec. 1960; poem (Box 22)
  - Harmon, Jim
    - The Depths, Dec. 1962; article (Box 22)
    - Vacation, Sept. 1957; article (Box 22)
  - Harris, Larry
    - The Importance of Being Important, Feb. 1963; article (Box 22)
    - The Question, Feb. 1963; article (Box 22)
  - Harris, Rosemary
    - Hamlin, Sept. 1961; article (Box 22)
  - Harrison, Harry
    - Captain Honario Harpplayer, R.N., March 1963; article (Box 22)
    - Famous First Words, Jan. 1964; article (Box 22)
    - Incident in the Ind., March 1964; article (Box 22)
    - Portrait of the Artist, Nov. 1964; article (Box 22)
    - Survival Planet, Aug. 1961; article (Box 22)
  - Hart, C.W., Jr.
    - Pseudo-Science and the Readers Guide, March 1957; article (Box 22)
  - Heinlein, Robert A.
    - The Door Into Summer, Oct.-Dec., 1956; book (Box 22)
    - Glory Road (Part I, II, III), 1963; book (Box 22)
    - Have Space Suit, Will Travel (Parts I, II), Aug.-Oct., 1958; book (Box 23)
    - Starship Soldier (Parts I, II), Oct.-Nov., 1959; book (Box 23)
  - Henderson, Zenna
    - Angels Unawares, March 1966; article (Box 23)
    - Deluge, 1963; article (Box 23)
    - The Last Step, Feb. 1958; article (Box 23)
    - And A Little Child, Oct. 1959; article (Box 23)
    - No Different Flesh, May 1965; article (Box 23)
    - Return, March 1961; article (Box 23)
    - Shadow on the Moon, March 1962; article (Box 23)
    - Subcommittee, July 1962; article (Box 23)
    - Things, July 1960; article (Box 23)
    - Troubling of the Water, Sept. 1966; article (Box 23)
    - Turn the Page, May 1957; article (Box 23)
    - Wilderness, Jan. 1957; article (Box 23)
    - Captivity, book (Box 23)
  - Henneburg, Charles
    - The Blind Pilot, Jan. 1960; article (Box 23)
    - Moon Fishers, April 1962; article (Box 23)
    - The Non-Humans, June 1960; article (Box 23)
  - Heriot, C.D.
    - Poltergeist, May 1961; article (Box 23)
  - Hetschel, Dick
    - The Tall Psychiatrist, March 1958; article (Box 23)
  - Hill, Hyacinthe
    - Inquest in Kansas, Nov. 1960; poem (Box 23)
    - Hodgins, Roderic C.
    - History of Dr. Frost, April 1964; article (Box 23)
  - Hoshi, Shin'ichi
    - Bokko-chan, 1963; article (translated by Noriyoshi Saito) (Box 23)
  - Howard, Robert E
    - For the Love of Barbara Allen, April 1966; article (Box 23)
  - Hoyle, Fred
    - A For Andromeda, undated; review (Box 23)
  - Hubbard, P.M.
    - The Golden Brick, 1963; article (Box 24)
    - Special Consent, 1963; article (Box 24)
    - Air Space Violated (printed copy), Nov., 1958; poem, original publication in Punch, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Huxley, Aldous
    - Chemical Persuasion, April 1959; article (printed copy) (Box 24)
  - Jackson, Shirley
    - The Missing Girl, Dec. 1957; article (Box 24)
    - The Omen, March 1958; article (Box 24)
  - Jakes, John
    - Hero At Work, Jan. 1957; article (Box 24)
    - Underfellow, May 1963; article (Box 24)
  - James, Kathleen
    - Blind God's Eye, March 1966; article (Box 24)
  - Janifer, Lawrence M.
    - Elementary, Sept. 1964; article (Box 24)
    - First Context, undated; article (Box 24)
  - Janivier, Paul
    - And Then She Found Him..., July 1957; article (Box 24)
    - There Ain't No Other Roads, March 1958; article (Box 24)
  - Jennings, Gary
    - A Murkle For Jesse, July 1965; article (Box 24)
    - Myrrha, 1962; article (Box 24)
  - Jesby, Edward
    - Sea Wrack, May 1964; article (Box 24)
  - Jonas, Gerald
    - The Mystery of the Purloined Grenouilles, Dec. 1966; article (Box 24)
  - Jones, L.E.
    - The Resentment of Jimsy Carew (printed copy), 1963; article (Box 24)
  - Jones, Leslie
    - The Devil and Mrs. Ackenbaugh, Aug. 1958; article (Box 24)
  - Kagan, Norman
    - Four Brands of Impossible, Aug. 1964; article (Box 24)
  - Kelley, Leo P.
    - O'Grady's Girl, Dec. 1965; article (Box 24)
  - Kelly, C. Brian
    - The Tunnel, Feb. 1961; article (Box 24)
  - Kerr, Walter H.
    - Gruesome Discovery at 242nd St. Feeding Station, Feb. 1963; poem (Box 24)
    - Treat, Nov. 1964; poem (Box 24)
  - Kersh, Gerald
    - The Terribly Wild Flowers, Oct. 1958; article (Box 24)
  - Keyes, Daniel
    - Crazy Maro, April 1960; article (Box 25)
    - Flowers for Algernon, April 1959; book (Box 25)
  - Kirk, Russell
    - Soworth Place, Nov. 1962; article (Box 25)
    - Beyond the Stumps, Dec. 1962; article (Box 25)
  - Kirs, Alex
    - Better Than Ever, Nov. 1965; article (Box 25)
  - Klein, Gerard
    - The Monster in the Park, Sept. 1961; article (translated by Virginia Kidd) (Box 25)
  - Knight, Damon
    - The Enemy, Jan. 1958; article (Box 25)
    - Eripmau, April 1958; article (Box 25)
    - Maid to Measure, Sept. 1964; article (Box 25)
    - The Night of Lies, March 1958; article (Box 25)
    - Stranger Station, undated; article (Box 25)
    - To Be Continued, Oct. 1959; article (Box 25)
    - Wine With Your Bottle, Sir, May 1959; article (Box 25)
    - The Tree of Time, 1963; book (Box 25)
    - Book reviews, 1959 (Box 25)
    - Books, 1960 (Box 25)
  - Kornbluth, C.M.
    - The Education of Tigress Macardle, July 1957; article (Box 25)
    - The Events Leading Down to Tragedy, Jan 1958; article (Box 25)
    - Ms. Found in a Chinese Fortune Cookie, July 1957; article (Box 25)
    - Theory of Rocketry, July 1958; article (Box 25)
    - Virginia, March 1958; article (Box 25)
    - The Deathsman, July 1958; book (Box 25)
    - The Unfortunate Typologist, March 1957; poem (Box 25)
  - Kurosaka, Bob
    - Those Who Can, Do, 1964; article (Box 25)
  - Kusenberg, Kurt
    - A Certain Room, Nov. 1960; article (Box 25)
  - La Farge, Oliver
    - Spud and Cochise, Dec. 1957; article (Box 26)
  - Lafferty, R.A
    - Hog-Belly Honey, May 1965; article (Box 26)
    - The Man With the Speckled Eyes, Dec. 1964; article (Box 26)
    - Narrow Valley, Sept. 1966; article (Box 26)
  - Lamb, Toni Heller
    - The Happy Place, June 1964; article (Box 26)
  - Lang, Allen Kim
    - Exchange Student, Feb. 1958; article (Box 26)
  - Langelaan, George
    - The Other Hand, Oct. 1961; article (Box 26)
  - Lardner, Rex
    - American Plan, May 1960; article (Box 26)
  - Laumer, Keith
    - Combat Unit, Nov. 1960; article (Box 26)
    - Founders Day, July 1966; article (Box 26)
    - Hybrid, article (Box 26)
  - Leahy, Jack
    - Newton Said, May 1963; article (Box 26)
  - Lefanu, Sheridan
    - The Dead Sexton, Jan., 1957; article (typescript and printed copy) (Box 26)
  - Lehrman, Herb
    - The Ancient Last, June 1956; short story contest winner (Box 26)
    - Revolt of the Potato Picker, Dec. 1966; article (Box 26)
  - Lieber, Fritz
    - The Big Trek, Oct. 1957; article (Box 26)
    - A Deskful of Girls, April 1958; article (Box 26)
    - Game for Motel Room, undated; article (Box 26)
    - Kindergarten, Nov. 1963; article (Box 26)
    - Last, Feb. 1957; article (Box 26)
    - Little Old Miss Macbeth, July 1958; article (Box 26)
    - The Man Who Made Friends With Electricity, undated; article (Box 26)
    - Mutterings From Underground, May 1962; article (Box 26)
    - Myths My Great-Granddaughter Taught Me, Oct. 1963; article (Box 26)
    - The Oldest Soldier, March 1960; article (Box 26)
    - Rump-Titty-Titty-Tum-Tah-Tee, May 1958; article (Box 26)
    - Success, July 1963; article (Box 26)
    - 237 Talking Statues, Etc., Sept. 1963; article (Box 26)
    - When the Change-Winds Blow, Aug., 1964; article (Box 26)
    - Four Ghosts in Hamlet, Jan. 1964; book (Box 26)
    - Book reviews, Dec. 1965 (Box 26)
  - Leinster, Murray
    - Anthropological Note, April 1957; article (Box 27)
    - The Case of the Homicidal Robots, Aug. 1961; book (Box 27)
  - Lewis, C. Day
    - The Antique Heroes, undated; poem (printed copy) (Box 27)
  - Lewis, C.S.
    - Ministering Angels, Jan. 1958; article (Box 27)
    - The Last of the Wine, July 1967; poem (published in Punch) (Box 27)
  - Lewis, Richard O.
    - The Docs, Dec. 1964; article (Box 27)
  - Lincoln, Victoria
    - No Evidence, April 1958; article (printed copy) (Box 27)
  - Lindsay, Dan
    - The Beatnik Werewolf, Dec. 1960; article (Box 27)
  - Lipsyte, Robert M.
    - Redman, Aug. 1964; article (Box 27)